# **RICK JOHNSON**

A Virtual Assistant with three years of experience, specializing in administrative support, calendar management, travel planning., and client relations. A strong history of planning events and identifying improvement opportunities for administrative functions. Adept at support ing onboarding procedures and HR functions for new hires.

123 Your Street, Nashville, TN 12345 rickjoh n\$on@exam ple.com (123)456-7890

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **VIRTUAL ASSISTANT**

Allen and Roberts Legal Associates, Nashville, TN September 2019 - Present

- Deliver administrative and secretarial support for legal and marketing departments, field phone inquiries, and schedule appointments and consultations
- Create agendasand manage calendars for firm lawyers, which includes coordinating travel planning, booking flights, and arranging lodging
- Conduct expense reporting for office supplies and interface with vendors to coordinate purchases and schedule delivery
- Create and manage client invoices, process payments, and communicate with
   c I i e nts to develop pay m e nt pl a ns and resolve i nvo ice d iscrepancies

### VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Gentile Legal Associates, Nashville, TN May 2018 - September 2019

- Provided administrative support to senior legal professionals, coordinated executive calendars, and managed communications with clients via phone and email
- Coordinated with the HRteam to develop new-hire onboarding plans and HR documentation, which included scheduling training orientations

#### **EDUCATION**

Associate of Arts (A.S.)
Communication
Nashville Community College,

Nashville Community Colleg Nashville TN May 2016 -May 2018

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- ♦ Administrative Support
- ♦ Microsoft Office Suite
- ♦ Travel Itineraries
- ♦ Calendar Management
- ♦ Written Communication

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

◆ Certified Administrative Professional (CAP), 2020